CHEN-YI HUANG (+886) 986 366 141 Chenyihuang001@gmail.com https://titaneric.github.io/

黃晨懿

in chen-yi-huang

Certified Kubernetes Administrator, dedicated software engineer, persistent learner, and enthusiastic open source contributor. Have 6 years experience in Python and 3 years experience in Linux administration. Skilled in automation of system administration, operation, monitoring, and cloud-native solution such as Kubernetes and Containerization. Confident in self-learning and large-scale code tracing. I'm honored to receive the Arctic Code Vault Contributor at GitHub and give short talks about Kubernetes metrics at K8s summit in 2021.

Skills

Observability Prometheus, Grafana, System & Kubernetes monitoring, Loki, Promtail

VM, Container Kubernetes, Docker, Linux SysAdmin, Nvidia Cloud-Native Technologies, Proxmox

Programming Python, Golang, C, Rust, PromQL

System, Networking Linux SysAdmin, TCP/IP, Wireshark, Chrome DevTools

IaC, CI/CD Ansible, Github Actions, Azure Pipelines

Language Chinese (native), English

Work Experience

May 2021-Present Senior Engineer, Intelligent Banking Division, E.SUN Bank Taipei, Taiwan.

- o Built, enhanced, and promoted comprehensive monitoring and alerting architecture on hundreds of servers, scraping up to 8-10 GB metrics per day.
- o 7 on-premise, total up to 40 nodes Kubernetes clusters administration, migration experience in - Development for data analysis, training (Al Cloud) with 95% SLA level.
 - Production API for model inferencing (MLaaS) with 99% SLA level.
- Experienced CentOS-based Linux SysAdmin, VM orchestration with Proxmox, and Nvidia Cloud Native Technologies with **hundreds** of GPU devices.
- Reduced manual intervention and automated the process of routine, task, and configuration change by developing Ansible playbook, Azure Pipelines, and calling RESTful/GraphQL API.
- Share experience with colleagues, help investigated, and resolved the issues in Ansible playbook, system and network administration, observability, and Kubernetes.

Oct 2020–Jan 2021 Engineer, Computer Integration Manufacturer, TSMC Hsinchu, Taiwan.

- Responsible for developing the agent and reporting APP for thousands of users in FAB.
- o Developed the web crawler to download hundreds of candidate resumes and general resume parser which achieved up to 95% extracted information accuracy.
- Wrote integration-test under possible scenarios and detailed documents including building procedure and class diagram for senior's project.
- o Pioneer of Robotic Process Automation and efficient i18n support for reporting APP.

July 2018-Jan 2019 Web Developer, CS COMPUTER CENTER, NCTU Hsinchu, Taiwan.

- Developed web services for hundreds of CS students, especially for Account Application System.
- Cooperated with teammate to discuss and design the suitable database schema and API routing.
- Participated and learned modern software development including testing, deployment, virtualized environments and CI/CD.

Education

2018–2020 Master of Data Science, Institute of Data Science & Engineering, National Chiao Tung University, Hsinchu, Taiwan.

2014–2018 Bachelor of Science, Department of Computer Science & Engineering, Yuan Ze University, Taoyuan, Taiwan.

Open Source Contributions

 Found the redundant calculation of derivative of power function in various deep learning frameworks.
© PyTorch, JAX, Autograd

Provide the HTTP delivery for forwarding article in BBS

@ Ptt-Backend

Data serialization and deserialization in Golang

@ go-bbs

Improved and beautified one of the example

@ Yew

Developed some code to be more Pythonic.

@ TensorFlow

Bug reporting

@ Python extension for Visual Studio Code

Participation of issue discussion.

@ Windows Subsystem for Linux

Talks & Slides share

Dec 2021 The Journey to the Kubernetes metrics @ Kubernetes Summit 2021.

May 2019 Buddy System.

Projects

May 2022 DCGM exporter extended for aliyun gpushare.

- Support aliyun gpushare-scheduler-extender in Nvidia dcgm-exporter
- o Provide k8s GPU instrumentation, monitoring solution in memory usage (MB) level

March 2021 Web Assembly rendering in Rust Playground.

- Renderred and displayed Web Assembly from compiled Rust code.
- o Support both Rust Playground (React) and mdBook (native JS) frontend rendering
- Support various wasm crates including wasm-pack, yew etc.

June 2020 Real-time Traffic Anomaly Detector.

- Anomaly detection in NCTU administration networks.
- Designed and implemented the data pre-processing pipeline with Apache Kafka, Spark and MongoDB.
- Processed data-stream in real time up to 30 kB/sec and transformed into feature vectors to further predict.

Sep 2019 **AutoDiff from Scratch**.

- o Simple neural network library supporting auto-differentiation
- Reported an issue and solved it in various deep-learning libraries during the development.
- Enabled high-level layer usage and had already tested on real-world dataset.

Master thesis

Title Solving Traveling Salesman Problem with the Kernel-enabled Attention

Supervisor Shi-Chun Tsai

Description We built on top of the prior state-of-the-art work who borrow the Transformer to solve the TSP. Motivated by the implicit dot product inside the kernel methods, we replace the scaled dot product with kernel in the attention mechanism. In our experiment, we archive shorter tour with a similar approach.

Certification & Award

- Certified Kubernetes Administrator (CKA)
- o Arctic Code Vault Contributor @ GitHub